let quiz = [
    {
        question: "Pregunta 1?",
        option: [
            "opcion 1",
            "opcion 2",
            "opcion 3",
            "opcion 4",
        ],
        answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Pregunta ?",
         option: [
            "opcion 1",
            "opcion 2",
            "opcion 3",
            "opcion 4",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Pregunta?",
         option: [
            "opcion 1",
            "opcion 2",
            "opcion 3",
            "opcion 4",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Pregunta?",
         option: [
            "opcion 1",
            "opcion 2",
            "opcion 3",
            "opcion 4",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "Pregunta?",
         option: [
            "opcion 1",
            "opcion 2",
            "opcion 3",
            "opcion 4",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "pregunta?",
         option: [
            "opcion 1",
            "opcion 2",
            "opcion 3",
            "opcion 4",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "pregunta?",
         option: [
            "opcion 1",
            "opcion 2",
            "opcion 3",
            "opcion 4",
        ],
        answer: 1,
    },
    {
        question:
            "pregunta?",
         option: [
            "opcion 1",
            "opcion 2",
            "opcion 3",
            "opcion 4",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Pregunta?",
         option: [
            "opcion 1",
            "opcion 2",
            "opcion 3",
            "opcion 4",
        ],
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Pregunta?",
         option: [
            "opcion 1",
            "opcion 2",
            "opcion 3",
            "opcion 4",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Pregunta?",
         option: [
            "opcion 1",
            "opcion 2",
            "opcion 3",
            "opcion 4",
        ],
        answer: 3,
    },
];
